### Experienced and passionate fullstack software engineer



shane@mediashane.com

1-801-410-3048

mediashane.com

linkedin.com/in/mediashane

github.com/mediashane

## About

I'm an experienced engineer who's shipped projects and products for some of the biggest brands and companies in the world. Web, mobile and desktop - I work in all environments with creativity, flexibility and reliability.

I'm capable of leading teams, working independently, or fitting in. Years of agency and freelance experience have conditioned me to adapt to and work with just about any tech, team or timeline.

I thrive in creative and friendly environments that give space for experimentation, independent thought and supportive collaboration.

### Skills

I have many years of experience in a variety of technologies, but I primarily focus on the JavaScript ecosystem in all of it's forms and formats. Here are a few technologies I've enjoyed working with recently and throughout my career:

- JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS
- React, React Native, Vue, Electron
- Node.js, Express.js, Passport.js

- PostgresSQL, NoSQL, SQL
- Next.js, Vercel, Supabase, Firebase
- GraphQL, REST

# Experience

#### Senior Lead Software Engineer, Koalition Interactive

2018 - Present | Remote, USA

- Shipped 20 projects and products for 26 clients using 23 different technologies
- Develop a wide variety of software across tech stacks and environments for mobile, web and desktop
- Lead teams and mentor developers to encourage growth, confidence and productivity
- Architect solutions for all aspects of development: frontend, backend, databases, servers and APIs

#### Web, iOS, and Android Engineer, MediaShane

2014 - 2018 | Remote, USA

• Build web and mobile apps using React, React Native, Node and modern Javascript

#### Web Developer, Attract/Interact

2016 - 2018 | Bend, OR

Customize and build additional functionality for WordPress websites and themes

#### Web Developer and Associate Producer, KUED Channel 7

2013 - 2014 | SLC, UT

- Develop the official kued.org website and produce associated digital content
- Research and produce short form documentaries on local social issues

#### Web Developer and Digital Media Specialist, Salt Lake City Public Library

2007 - 2012 | SLC, UT

- Lead developer and administrator of all things digital (website, intranet, social networks, media content)
- · Research and implement new technology trainings, services and programs

#### Web Developer, Red Butte Garden

2009 | SLC, UT

Developed and maintained the official redbuttegarden.org

#### Database Administrator, Utah Museum of Fine Arts

2004 - 2005 | SLC, UT

• Administered fund-raising and membership database

# Education